Speech Department Office Files 1948-1974
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Speech Department Office Files
1948-1974
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
Archives 3
2.5 linear feet 5 containers
Included in these materials are data relating to the development of the Department and its teaching activities, planning of the Performing Arts Coliseum, and typed manuscripts for three publications of E.E. Ettlich.
Included in these materials are data relating to the development of the Department and its teaching activities, planning of the Performing Arts Coliseum, and typed manuscripts for three publications of E.E. Ettlich.
The Collection is open for research use.
These records were acquired by Bruce C. Harding, University records manager on November 12, 1976 from the files of the Department of Speech in Daggy Hall, Room 201. Transfer of these files to UniversityArchives is provided by the state retention schedule (GAA53) prepared for that office.
Ettlich, Ernest E.--Archives
Washington State University. Dept. of Speech--Archives; State College of Washington. Dept. of Speech--Archives; Washington State University. Dept. of Speech--Records and correspondence
Speech communication (Linguistics)--Washington (State)
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- President - C.C. French, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Dean of Faculty - S. Town stephenson, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AcademicVice President - Allan H. Smith, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Executive Vice President - W. Beasley, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Educational Policies Committee - Manual, n.d (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Business and Finace Vice President - W. bishop/V. Shelton, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Business Vice President - Carl Pettibone, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Affirmative Action Office, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Controller's Offive, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Facilities Planning, 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Acting Dean - Sciences and Arts, H.J. Wood, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dean - Sciences and Arts, Stephen R. Mitchell, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Dean - Sciences and Arts, T.H. Kennedy, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2a)
- Sciences and Arts Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Humanites Department Chiarman - Staff Meetings, 1949-1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Registrar, 1960-1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Purchasing, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Graduate School, 1960-1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Graduate School, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- American Studies Program, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- English Department, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Continuing Education, 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Summer School, 1947-1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Staff Meetings - Department, 1948-1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Faculty Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Faculty Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1a)
- Faculty Minutes - Executive Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Faculty Minutes - Executive Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2a)
- Newsletter, Vol. I and II, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Newsletter, Vol. III, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 3a)
- Newsletter, Vol. IV, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 3b)
- Newsletter, Vol. V, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 3c)
- Newsletter, Vol. VI and VII, 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 3d)
- Newsletter, Vol. VIII - X, 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 3e)
- Coliseum Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Honors Council Program, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Humanistic Center, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rules and Procedures for Incompletes - EPC Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Graduation Requirements Revision, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Graduation Hours - EPC Sub-Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Scholarship Selections, 1960-1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- An Introduction to Parliamentary Procedure - E.E. Ettlich, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Jonathan Edwards: A Study in Audience - E.E. Ettlich, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Western Oratory Studies - H.H. Spaulding - E.E. Ettlich, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Speech Education - 1970 - E.E. Ettlich, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Newsletter, Vols. I-V and VII-VIII, 1969-1976 (Box 5, Folder 13)